A Guide to the University of Virginia Vice President for Development Office Administrative Files, [1969] 1977-1984
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
University of Virginia Vice President for Development Office Administrative Files [1969] 1977-1984
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-25/1/1.852
This collection consists of 8,500 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the library on 1986 February 21.
Scope and Content Information
Administrative files, including case files of various fund-raising efforts, correspondence, newspaper clippings, and memoranda, concerning all segments of the university community.
Contents List
- Acknowledgements--Alderman Library (3 folders) 1977-1981 (Box 1)
- Acknowledgements--Alumni Fund-Restricted Use (2 folders) 1979-1981 (Box 1)
- Acknowledgements--Alumni Fund-Unrestricted Use 1979 (Box 1)
- Acknowledgements--Bayly Museum (3 folders) 1977-1981 (Box 1)
- Acknowledgements--Corporate Gifts 1978 (Box 1)
- Acknowledgements--Darden School and Darden Sponsors 1977-1978 (Box 1)
- Acknowledgements--School of Education and Foundation 1977-1978 (Box 1)
- Acknowledgements--Engineering School (2 folders) 1977-1979 (Box 1)
- Acknowledgements--Foundation Gifts (2 folders) 1977-1979 (Box 1)
- Acknowledgements--Law School (2 folders) 1977-78, 1981 (Box 1)
- Acknowledgements--Law School Foundation 1977-1978 (Box 1)
- Box 2
- Acknowledgements--Law School and Law School Foundation 1979 (Box 2)
- Acknowledgements--Matching Gift Corporate 1977-1979 (Box 2)
- Acknowledgements--Medical Center 1979 (Box 2)
- Acknowledgements--Medical School and Medial School Foundation (2 folders) 1977-1979 (Box 2)
- Acknowledgements--Miscellaneous (3 folders) 1977-1980 (Box 2)
- Parent Gifts Acknowledgements (2 folders) 1977-1979 (Box 2)
- Acknowledgements--Scholarship (2 folders) 1977-1979 (Box 2)
- Acknowledgement--Scott Stadium (2 folders) 1977-1979 (Box 2)
- Acknowledgements--U.VA. Fund--Unrestricted Use 1977-1978 (Box 2)
- Acknowledgements--U.VA. Fund--Restricted Use 1977-1978 (Box 2)
- Acknowledgements 1977 Apr (Box 3)
- Admissions, Office of 1979-1981 (Box 3)
- Admissions Acceptances 1977 Fall (Box 3)
- Admissions Letters Invitees--August 28th 1976-1977 (Box 3)
- Admissions (2 folders) 1980 Fall (Box 3)
- Advanced Studies, Center for (2 folders) 1977-1981 (Box 3)
- Alderman Library 1959-1974 (Box 3)
- Alderman Library 1976-1978 (Box 3)
- Alderman Library 1979-Present (Box 4)
- Alderman Library Holsinger Collection 1960-1981 (Box 4)
- Alumni Association Material 1976-1981 (Box 4)
- Alumni Board of Trustees of the U.VA. Endowment Fund 1979-1981 (Box 4)
- Alumni Fund Material 1978-1981 (Box 4)
- Arboretum Committee n.d. (Box 4)
- Architecture, School of 1978-1982 (Box 4)
- Architecture, School of--Alumni Association 1973-1979 (Box 4)
- Art, McIntire Department of 1981-1982 (Box 4)
- Arts and Sciences, College of 1971-1982 (Box 4)
- Arts and Sciences, Graduate School 1975-1981 (Box 5)
- Athletic Department 1978-1981 (Box 5)
- Audit Department 1979 (Box 5)
- Bayly Museum Advisory Board Invitations 1977-1979 (Box 5)
- Bayly Museum (4 folders) 1976-1982 (Box 5)
- Biology, Department of 1980 (Box 5)
- Birdwood Estate (2 folders) 1972-1980 (Box 5)
- Blandy Experimental Farm 1978 (Box 5)
- Business Operations, Office of 1978-1980 (Box 5)
- Campaign 1981 (Box 5)
- Career Opportunities Institute--Fund Raising and Publicity 1979-1984 (Box 5)
- Career Opportunities Institute-Program Description, etc. 1979-1981 (Box 6)
- Career Planning and Placement, Office of 1979-1982 (Box 6)
- Cavalier Daily 1978 (Box 6)
- Center for Innovative technology 1984 (Box 6)
- Chemical Engineering, Department of 1977-1979 (Box 6)
- Chemistry, Department of 1977-1982 (Box 6)
- Child--Care Center 1982 (Box 6)
- Children's Medical Center 1983-1984 (Box 6)
- Class of '52-'53 Reunion--Planning, Programs, etc 1974-1978 (Box 6)
- Classics, Department of 1978-1980 (Box 6)
- Colonnade Club 1981 (Box 6)
- Commerce, McIntire School of 1977-1984 (Box 6)
- Commerce, School of--Alumni Association 1973-1979 (Box 6)
- Computing Activities, Office of 1978-1982 (Box 6)
- Continuing Education, School of 1977-1983 (Box 6)
- Corporate Acknowledgements for 1980 1979-1980 (Box 6)
- Darden GSBA (2 folders) 1977-1978 (Box 6)
- Darden GSBA (3 folders) 1979-Present (Box 7)
- Darden GSBA--Sponsors 1977-1981 (Box 7)
- Deans Meetings 1980 (Box 7)
- Declaration, The 1976 (Box 7)
- Development 1981-1984 (Box 7)
- Echols Scholars Program 1983-1984 (Box 7)
- Economics Department File 1980-1982 (Box 7)
- Education, School of 1976-1984 (Box 7)
- Education, School of-Foundation 1975-1979 (Box 7)
- EEO (Equal Employment Office?) 1983 (Box 7)
- Eminent Scholars n.d. (Box 7)
- Energy Policy Studies Center 1978-1979 (Box 7)
- English, Department of 1981 (Box 8)
- Environmental Sciences 1976-1982 (Box 8)
- Faculty Wives of U.VA. 1979 (Box 8)
- Foundation Gifts Acknowledgements for 1980 1979-1980 (Box 8)
- Garden Club of Virginia n.d. (Box 8)
- General, University 1976-1978 (Box 8)
- Gilmer Hall 1983 (Box 8)
- Glee Club, University 1980 (Box 8)
- Government and Foreign Affairs Dept, of 1978-1982 (Box 8)
- Guide Service, University 1976-1980 (Box 8)
- History, Department of 1978-1982 (Box 8)
- Honor System 1982-1983 (Box 8)
- Hospital 1982-1984 (Box 8)
- Institute for Environmental Negotiation 1984 (Box 8)
- Institute of Government 1979-1980 (Box 8)
- Institutional Analysis, Office of 1979 (Box 8)
- Inter-Sorority Council 1977 (Box 8)
- International Council 1984 (Box 8)
- Jackson, Luther P.--House 1977 (Box 8)
- Jefferson Scholars 1981-1983 (Box 8)
- Jefferson Buildings and Grounds 1983-1984 (Box 8)
- Judge Advocate General School 1981 (Box 8)
- Law School 1976-1983 (Box 8)
- Law School Alumni Association 1979 (Box 8)
- Law School Foundation (2 folders) 1975-1983 (Box 9)
- Law School Foundation Acknowledgements for 1980 1980 (Box 9)
- LEAD Program 1982 (Box 9)
- Madison House 1979-1982 (Box 9)
- Mail Service--University 1980 (Box 9)
- Medical Center, U.VA 1977-1984 (Box 9)
- Medicine, School of 1976-1984 (Box 9)
- Medical School--Acknowledgements (2 folders) 1980-1982 (Box 9)
- Medical Alumni Association 1975-1976 (Box 9)
- Medical Alumni Board 1981 (Box 9)
- Medical School Foundation 1976-1981 (Box 9)
- Miller Center [White Burkett Miller Center] 1969-1982 (Box 9)
- Miller Center [White Burkett Miller Center] 1980-1983 (Box 10)
- Miller Center--Fund Raising Only 1976-1979 (Box 10)
- Miscellaneous Acknowledgements for 1980 1975-1980 (Box 10)
- Molecular Genetics Institute 1982 (Box 10)
- Music Department 1977-1982 (Box 10)
- Neurology, Department of 1976-1982 (Box 10)
- Neurosurgery 1981 (Box 10)
- Nuclear Engineering 1983 (Box 10)
- Nurse s Alumni Association 1975-1976 (Box 10)
- Nursing, School of 1978-1981 (Box 10)
- OB-GYN, Department of 1979-1980 (Box 10)
- Oceans Law and Policy, Center for 1978-1982 (Box 10)
- Parapsychology 1978 (Box 10)
- Parents 1977-1978 (Box 10)
- Patent Foundation, University of Virginia Alumni 1977-1983 (Box 10)
- Pediatrics 1980 (Box 10)
- Pharmacology, Department of 1977 (Box 10)
- Philanthropic, Department of n.d. (Box 10)
- Philosophy, Department of 1980 (Box 10)
- Physics, Department of 1977-1978 (Box 10)
- Polo Club 1978-1980 (Box 10)
- Psychology, Department of 1978 (Box 10)
- Raven Society 1978-1979 (Box 10)
- Recommendations and Acknowledgements A-Z 1976-1977 (Box 10)
- Religious Studies, Department of 1981 (Box 11)
- Research, Associate Provost for 1981 (Box 11)
- Residential Councils, The Associate of 1976 (Box 11)
- Residential Colleges 1967-1972 (Box 11)
- Risk Management and Safety, Department of 1980 (Box 11)
- Russian and European Studies, Center for 1981 (Box 11)
- State Council for Higher Education in Virginia (SCHEV) 1979-1980 (Box 11)
- Scholarships 1983 (Box 11)
- Scott Stadium 1975-1976 (Box 11)
- Scott Stadium 1975-1978 (Box 11)
- Scott Stadium (Special) 1974 (Box 11)
- Slavic Languages and Literature, Department of 1977 (Box 11)
- Society of Artemis 1978 (Box 11)
- Sociology, Department of 1978 (Box 11)
- S. Asians Studies File 1978 (Box 11)
- Society of the Cincinnati in Virginia n.d. (Box 11)
- Speech and Drama, Department of 1981 (Box 11)
- Sponsored Programs, Office of 1981 (Box 11)
- Sports Department. Intramural Recreational 1979-1980 (Box 11)
- Student Affairs 1979-1981 (Box 11)
- Student Council 1978 (Box 11)
- Student Health Faculty 1984 (Box 11)
- Student Information System, University of Virginia 1978 (Box 11)
- Summer Session 1978-1980 (Box 11)
- Surgery, Department of 1979 (Box 11)
- Theatre 1981 (Box 11)
- Thomas Jefferson Award 1978 (Box 11)
- Tocqueville Society 1979 (Box 11)
- Truman Scholarship Fund 1982 (Box 11)
- University Affiliated Organizations 1980 (Box 11)
- University Alumni in Congress n.d. (Box 12)
- University of Virginia Fund 1982 (Box 12)
- University Village 1978 (Box 12)
- Urology, Department of 1979-1980 (Box 12)
- Virginia Chapter of the Arthritis Foundation, Inc. n.d. (Box 12)
- Virginia Foundation for Humanities and Public Policy 1983 (Box 12)
- Virginia Graduate Marine Science Consortium 1983 (Box 12)
- Virginia Historic Landmarks--UVA 1984 (Box 12)
- Virginia Lung Association n.d. (Box 12)
- Virginia Student Aid Foundation 1978-1981 (Box 12)
- Virginia Student Aid Foundation (9 folders) 1978 Jan-Sept (Box 12)
- Virginia Student Aid Foundation (8 folders) 1978-1979 May (Box 13)
- Virginia Student Aid Foundation--Less 1979 Oct (7 folders) 1979 Jul-1980 Jan (Box 14)
- Virginia Student Aid Foundation--Less 1980 Apr (9 folders) 1980 Feb-Nov (Box 15)
- Virginia Student Aid Foundation--Less 1981 Mar (10 folders) 1980 Nov-1981 Sept (Box 16)
- Virginia Student Aid Foundation--Letters (2 folders) 1981 Oct-Dec (Box 17)
- Virginia Student Aid Foundation--Answered, Current 1982 (Box 17)
- Virginia Student Aid Foundation 1982 Apr-Jul (Box 17)
- Virginia Student Aid Foundation White Burkett Miller Center see Miller Center 1982 May-Jun (Box 17)
- Wilmington Area Campaign n.d. (Box 17)
- Woodson Institute 1982-1984 (Box 17)